trifectanutrition.com 2016-11-29

# Trifecta Privacy Policy

TRIFECTA STATEMENT OF PRIVACY

Trifecta is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to Trifecta website and governs data collection and usage at all Trifectas sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the Trifecta Statement of Privacy. Trifecta is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.

COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

As an E-commerce website, Trifecta collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by Trifecta is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. Trifecta does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.

Trifecta encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Trifecta so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Trifecta website.

USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Trifecta and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested. It is possible that Trifecta may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Trifecta and its affiliates. Trifecta may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Trifecta does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Trifecta may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Trifecta does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Trifecta may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Trifecta or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Trifecta, including its website; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Trifecta or the public.

Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Trifecta or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Trifecta abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Trifecta offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences by emailing info@trifectanutrition.com. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records.

You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Trifecta by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.

CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

Trifecta will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Trifecta will use your personal information, Trifecta will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Trifecta encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Trifecta is protecting your information.

© Trifecta 2015 All Rights Reserved

TRIFECTA SECURITY POLICY

Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.

© Trifecta 2015 All Rights Reserved
